mobigyaan.com 2011-11-13

# Privacy Policy

**P** **rivacy Policy**

 **Introduction**

MobiGyaan.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. If you have any questions or comments about our policy, please feel free to contact us.

 **Personal Information**  
The personal information you enter on MobiGyaan.com is not for sale. Using MobiGyaan.com will not cause you to receive unsolicited email. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
Advertisements that appear on MobiGyaan.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. MobiGyaan.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on MobiGyaan.com unless you choose to share it with them.

Our main third party advertiser is Google Adsense

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

This privacy policy covers the use of MobiGyaan.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers and we do not have access to this information.

 **Direct Marketing**  
We may also use Your Personal Information, or permit selected third parties to use Your Personal Information, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by e-mail or SMS

 **Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Links**  
MobiGyaan.com may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by MobiGyaan.com. We are not responsible for any offers given by our clients.

You can send email to mobigyaan@live.com

Comments:
